The radiance of the night shines through my window
but the path to immortality is long.
The Eight Views and Nine-Bend Streams are desolate.
Living beings question the miseries of the world over a jar of wine.
Forget about Nirvana and rebirth,
I will break through the waves with my own flesh and blood.
The heavens are vast, so what if I was born mediocre ?
I stare at the Dao in my moments of madness
as the storm rages just below.
I've been thinking about life and death in my dreams.
I've unsheathed my sword to ask the immortals
why the world is a-changing.
Heaven and earth reveals its poignant truths.
Swallow the Four Seas and the Eight Wastelands,
experience all the vicissitudes of life in an instant.
I will defy the light in the sky
to continue to write a new chapter for all things in the three realms of existence.
Just a thought separates mortal from immortal.
Transform your insignificant body into light.
The hardships of the journey
will temper this young man's heart.
If I become a Renegade Immortal, will I hesitate to fight the heavens ?
Renegade Immortal
Subtitles by Bonobosubs
https://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Greetings, envoy of the Foreign Battlefield.
The Foreign Battlefield cleanup will now begin.
Open the gate !
It has been 3 months.
The disciples can exit the valley.
Only 1 of the 7 tokens remains.
It seems the competition was fierce this year.
This will be fun to watch.
What !?
One person took all the tokens ?
That's complete nonsense.
It's true !
He killed almost all of our people !
He's here...
He's here ! This is his aura !
Since you're here,
stop hiding !
Teng Huayuan !
Do you dare to fight me ?
He's just Early stage Foundation Establishment.
How can you all be so scared ?
Teng Huayuan,
give me my parents' souls !
Nascent Soul !?
How can a Nascent Soul cultivator enter Jue Ming Valley ?
How could you improve your cultivation so much
in such a short time ?
You are the one
that made me who I am today !
It really is him...
It makes sense if he's Nascent Soul...
Jue Ming Valley only allows
Foundation Establishment cultivators to enter it.
How did he become so powerful ?
How could someone reach Nascent Soul so quickly ?
It's just been a few days
but his cultivation has improved this much...
This aura...
Middle stage Nascent Soul !?
An illusion ?
You deceitful bastard,
show yourself !
He must be too scared to fight
and has fled long ago.
He just left a little toy for you to play with.
He even managed to fool all the Ancestors here.
Wang Lin, oh Wang Lin,
I knew you weren't this skilled.
If you don’t show yourself now,
I hope you won't blame me
for crushing your parents' souls !
The Soul Flag...
Stop !
The first time was an illusion
but this time it's the real you.
Wang Lin,
is this all you’ve got ?
Explode !
Blue Ice !?
Interesting...
Not only does this kid have Illusion City's Thousand Illusions Bead
but he also has the Underworld Sect's Blue Ice.
That flying sword is no ordinary weapon either.
Although it's an imitation,
it's still powerful.
The real show is yet to come.
It's now or never !
Father,
Mother,
sorry for being late.
Explode !
Formation, activate !
Back then, you killed my grandson.
But today,
I will extract your soul and refine it in this Soul Flag.
You will suffer the cruelest of tortures before your death !
I, a Nascent Soul Ancestor,
was played by a mere Foundation Establishment brat.
The most frightening thing
is how decisive and resilient this guy is.
To prevent the explosion from spreading,
he severed his own arm without any hesitation.
If it were anyone else,
I would've admired them.
But this kid...
I will let you enjoy being devoured by your own parents.
Father...
Mother...
Tie Zhu is unfilial...
Without me
you wouldn’t have suffered this fate.
Wang Lin,
look how kind I am !
I let you reunite with your parents...
Father... Mother...
From now on,
your son will never leave you.
My fate will depend on this !
Did you think
I’d let you use that strange teleportation again ?
All 7 tokens were destroyed.
That means the gate will close very soon.
That old bastard Teng Huayuan !
The last token has been destroyed.
That means the gate to the Foreign Battlefield will close.
500 years... We waited 500 years for nothing !
We wasted 500 years...
The Corpse Sect's disciples are all dead.
That means Luo Sha won't get to enter.
So what will he do with my body now ?
Wang Lin...
You deserve to have
a painful death.
Alright, I'm done playing.
I had already guessed
that you’d try to escape to the Foreign Battlefield.
You can give up on that idea.
How ridiculous,
how can an Ancestor like me be afraid of a Foundation Establishment brat ?
Go !
Li'er...
Grandfather has avenged you.
After his body is devoured,
I will extract his soul
and make him suffer the cruelest of tortures.
So what if it was a debt of blood ?
Does the reason really matter ?
The strong prey on the weak,
that’s all this is.
You old fool,
we’ve seen this countless times already.
Why are you spouting such nonsense now ?
This is the first time in 10 000 years
that a Foundation Establishment cultivator challenged a Nascent Soul Ancestor.
His determination is admirable
but his situation is pitiful.
We should feel ashamed...
Is this what the love of a child should be ?
Father...
Mother...
Did I make a mistake ?
Heng Yue Sect...
Zhang Hu...
Teng Li...
Wang Family Village...
Is weakness itself a sin ?
Cultivation !
So this is what cultivation is !
I get it...
I get it !
Killing intent ?
What is this killing intent ?
Father...
Mother...
Tie Zhu is unfilial.
If there’s a next life,
I hope I won't be your son
because I am...
unworthy.
Sigh...
Is this !?
Don't you dare escape with my bead !
The gate to the Foreign Battlefield is closed.
None of Zhao's sects qualified to enter !
Foreign Battlefield
Senior Sister, have a look !
I’ve already removed half a sleeve.
Ma Liang
War God Shrine disciple
Late stage Foundation Establishment
Let's not waste time.
We were lucky enough
to have found this piece of armor.
Zhou Zihong
War God Shrine disciple
Late stage Foundation Establishment
I had heard that
just breathing the air here boosts cultivation.
We fought so hard to get in
but we're just scavenging for armor.
Don’t underestimate this armor.
Don't you see the Giant Demon Clan's mark on his forehead ?
If we take this armor,
we will have spiritual energy for years.
What’s that ?
Let's follow it.
Is this...
A spatial rift.
The Ancestor once said
that during the Foreign Battlefield cleanups,
the space might not withstand
the battles between cultivators
so it's torn into spatial rifts.
If a cultivator is swallowed by a rift,
they will become a wandering soul
and will never be able to return to the mortal world.
That was a close call.
I'm glad we weren't too close.
Damn spatial rift...
You stole one of my treasures !
Where’s the treasure ?
It flew over there
and was swallowed by the spatial rift.
A Giant Demon Clan member ?
Their people can change their appearance
when they reach Soul Transformation.
Maybe he is Soul Transformation
since he has a human form.
What a pity...
Wang Lin,
I used all my remaining energy
to open the gate to the Foreign Battlefield
and save your soul.
I will now fall into a deep slumber.
From now on
your fate
is in your own hands.
Killing intent is a fluctuation of spiritual energy around someone reflecting their mental state and intention to kill. The more someone kills, the more killing intent they accumulate in their body and the stronger their killing intent becomes.
You can think of killing intent as an aura around someone that can be sensed by others.
I've been walking this path for endless years
just to catch a glimpse of your silhouette.
Is it the compass of fate
that wrote this outcome for us ?
The heavens want to erase your existence,
that's the obsession guiding me.
Is this the path to uncover
truths from falsehoods ?
In a world of murk and shadow,
only the flame of truth can light the way.
Look at them all,
being carried by the waves.
being drowned.
I don't want to believe in whoever decides fate,
I will let the world refine my soul.
So what if I become an Immortal and defy the heavens ?
I will fight.
I'll break through the abyss of despair
to finally learn who I really am.
My body is stained by the bloody color of slaughter,
I embrace this obsession.
I won't glance back at the wasteland I left behind.
Even if this suffering shatters my soul
and I'm reborn countless times in hell,
I'll still fight.
It's hard to avoid loneliness
when you are above everyone else.
Can a moth that has witnessed the flames of a Suzaku
be afraid of a firefly ?